<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-14T14:49:44+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tal</title><subtitle>Just another software developer&apos;s blog named after a cat.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Getting an A+</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/it/certifications/blogs/anki/2023/08/28/Getting-an-A+.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Getting an A+" /><published>2023-08-28T06:11:00+04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T06:11:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/it/certifications/blogs/anki/2023/08/28/Getting-an-A+</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/it/certifications/blogs/anki/2023/08/28/Getting-an-A+.html"><![CDATA[<p>Talking to non-departmental IT support professionals in Sharjah, the A+ isn’t the clincher for all their duties, but it is a foundation if nothing else. They recommended I get more comfortable with Windows and Windows server.</p>

<p>The CompTIA A+ certification has a lot of material for practice, and there is a wonderful ~10 hr course on YouTube by the channel Professor Messer, who offers additional materials and the like on his site.</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?si=29XXg4-pwVPkyKoW&amp;list=PLG49S3nxzAnnOmvg5UGVenB_qQgsh01uC" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>

<p>For my part, I jotted notes - splitting them where possible. There are a lot of names - and x10 as many acronyms.</p>

<p>I wrote the notes on the terminal with Neovim, and saved them on separate csv files. I put them all in one deck, but tagged each file’s import with its appropriate tag.</p>

<p>Furthermore, I will also update the deck with media files - even though I mostly avoid them.</p>

<p>Remembering what a molex connector or any other interface/connector/header looks like would be helpful.</p>

<p>Now it’s time to learn something else, while reviewing the cards as I forget - Spaced Repetition has rarely let me down with school and university after all.</p>

<p>What’s next for my extra-curriculars is a deeper dive into Windows for client and server systems.</p>

<p>Professor Messer has a YouTube playlist for it of the same time commitment. Though I suppose too I should supplement my learning with some written material.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="IT" /><category term="Certifications" /><category term="Blogs" /><category term="Anki" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to non-departmental IT support professionals in Sharjah, the A+ isn’t the clincher for all their duties, but it is a foundation if nothing else. They recommended I get more comfortable with Windows and Windows server.]]></summary></entry></feed>